Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Photographs of Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of Yale Faculty, Circa 1966-2005; Accession 2011-A-025
  - Pelli, Cesar, 1978 - 1984 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Peluso, Nancy L., 1994 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Pepine, Arthur, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Perlis, Vivian, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Perlotto, Dr. James, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Permut, Steven, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Perrone, Kathryn, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Perrotti, James, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Perrow, Charles B., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Peterdi, Gabor F., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Peters, Jean Kon, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Peterson, Dr. Bradley, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Peterson, Linda, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Peucker, Brigitte, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Pfefferle, Lisa D., 1992 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Philllips, Kristin, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Phillips, Peter C.B., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Piatetski-Shapiro, Ilya, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Pickett, Lawrence K., Undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Pierce, Patricia, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Pierson, George W., Undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Plantinga, Leon B., 1992 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Plattus, Alan, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Poirion, Daniel, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Polak, Benjamin, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Pollitt, Jerone, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Polinger, Karen Foster, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Pollak, Anne Marie and Karoline, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Pollard, Robert D., 2001 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Pollen, Gale, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Pope, John C., Undated (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Pope, John C., Undated (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Pope, Marvin, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Porter, Charles Prof., 1997 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Pospisil, Leopold J., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Potenza, Marc, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Price, Martin, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Prichard, Dr. James, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Prinstein, Mitch, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Prown, Jules D., 1979 - 1990 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Pruett, Kyle (M.D.), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Prusoff, William H., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Pupedis, Raymond J., 1994 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Pustejovsky, Brandon, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Puziss, John, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Quinlan, Donald M., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Quint, David, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Rabe, Karin M., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Radding, Charles (M.D.), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Rae, Douglas, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Rakic, Pasko, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Ramos, Val, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Ranalli, George J., 1979 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Rand, Paul, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Randolph, Theodore W., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Ranis, Gustav, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Rawson, Claude, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Read, Nicholas, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Rebhun, Linda-Anne, Undated (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Redmond, D. Eugene Jr., 1985 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Reed, Prof. Mark, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Reed, Victoria, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Regan, Lynne, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Reich, Herbert J., Undated (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Reifsnyder, William E., 1980, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Reiger, Susan, Undated (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Reiser, Morton (M.D.), 1986 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Reisman, W. Michael, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Remington, Charles, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Renouf, Nicholas, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Renouf, Nicholas, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Rephann, Richard, 1990, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Reynolds III, Jock M., 1998, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Reynolds, Lloyd G., 1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Reznick, J. Steven, 1992, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Richard, Alison F., 1994, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Richard, Alison F., 1990, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Richards, Frank F. (M.D.), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Richards, Frederick M., 1989, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Richards, Lloyd, 1979, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Richart, Charles E., 1963, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Riley, Margaret (Peg), 1996 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Ritchie, Murdoch, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Ritner, Robert K., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Rittgers, Ronald, Undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Ritvo, Samuel (M.D.), 1993 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Roach, Prof. Joseph R., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Roach, Kevin, Undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Robertson, William D., 1960 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Robertson, William D., 1960 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Robinson, Dorothy K., 1978, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Robinson, Duncan, 1983, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Robinson, Fred C., 1977 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Robinson, James E. (M.D.), 1979 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Robinson, Marc, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Rodgers, John, 1968, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Rodin, Judith, 1979, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Rodriguez, Cesar, 1988, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Rodriguez, Daisy, 1994, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Roeder, Kathryn, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Roeder, Shirleen, 1984 - 2001 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Roemer, John E., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Roemer, Michael, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Rogers, John, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Rogers, Rutherford, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Rokhlin, Vladimir, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Rose-Ackerman, Susan, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Roseman, Ronald, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Rosenbaum, Joel L., Undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Rosenthal, Franz, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Rosner, Daniel, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Ross, Arthur M., Undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Ross, Stephen A., 1985 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Roth, Dr. Robert H., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Rouse, Irving, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Routh, Donald, 1993, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Rowe, Michael, Undated (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Rubin, Philip, Undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Ruddle, Frank, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Ruddle, Nancy H., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Ruderman, David, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Rudich, Vasily, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Rudin, Harry R., Undated (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Ruff, Willie H. Jr., 1991 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Ruggles, Richard, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Russell, Letty, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Russett, Bruce M., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Russett, Cynthia E., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Ruth, Lester, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Ryan, Mark B., 1977 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Ryden, John, 1979 - 1991 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Ryder, Robert, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Rye, Danny, Undated (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Ryle, Anne E., Undated (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Sachdev, Subir, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Sacks, Herbert S. (M.D.), 1996-2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Sadler, Lois, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Salinas, Shannon, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Salovey, Peter, 1988 - 2001 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Saltzman, Barry, 1972 - 2003 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Sammons, Jeffrey L., 1979, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Samuel, Harold E., 1988, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Sandweiss, Jack, 1977, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Sanneh, Lamin, 1990, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Sanneh, Sandra, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Sarason, Seymour B, 1979 - 1999 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Sarrel, Phillip and Lorna, 1970 - 1988 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Sartorelli, Alan, 1977 - 1987 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Saunders, Martin, 1965 - 1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Savage, Barbara, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Sarage, I. Richard, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Savo, Cynthia, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Sawyer-Parisot, Elisabeth, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Scarf. Jerbert E/, 1976 - 1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Schaefer, Bradley, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Schenker, Alexander, 1965 - 1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Schepartz, Alanna, 1990, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Schiff, Judith, 1977 - 1992 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Schiffries, Prof. Craig, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Schilling, Lynne S., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Schlener, Denise, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Schmidt, Benno, 1986 - 1992 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Schmir, Gaston, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Schoolfield, George, 1977 - 1990 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Schor, Naomi, Undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Schottenfeld, Richard, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Schowalter, John (M.D.), 1977 - 1989 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Schrader, George A. Jr., 1963 - 1987 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Schuck, Peter H., 1983 - 1991 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Schultheiss, Peter, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Schultz, Martin, 1977 - 1986 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Schultz, Robert J., 1977 - 1992 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Schwab-Stone, Dr. Mary E., 1991 - 1995 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Schwartz, Linda A., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Schwartz, Peter (M.D.), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Schwartz, Stuart, Undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Scofield, Margaret, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Scott, james C., 1977 - 1997 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Scully, Carol, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Scully, Vincent J., 1979 - 2001 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Sears, Marvin, 1965 - 1982 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Seashore, Margretta, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Sedivy, John M., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Seagraves, William, Undated (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Seilacher, Adolf, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Seligman, George, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Seligson, David (M.D.), 1970 - 1987 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Selzer, Richard A. 9M.D.), 1968 - 1977 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Sewall, Richrd B., 1976 - 1992 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Sexton, Dorothy L., 1978 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Shank, Richard R., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Shankar, Ramamurti, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Shapiro, Ian, 1999, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Sharp, Pat, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Shaumyan, Sebastian, 1975 - 1986 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Shaw, Richard H., 1992 - 1998 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Sheard, Michael (M.D.), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Sheffield, Frederick, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Shepherd, Dr. Gordon, 1985 - 1991 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Sherman, Philip, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Sherman, Robert B., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Shiller, Robert J., 1999 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Shope, Robert (M.D.), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Shpitalnik, Vladimir, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Shubik, Martin, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Shuman, Robert G., 1994 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Shuman, D. Ellen, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Shumway, Floyd, Undated (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Siccama, Thomas, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Siedlecki, John, 1996 - 1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Siegel, Reva B., 1999 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Sierra-Honigmann, Dr. Maria, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Siggins, Lorraine (M.D.), 1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sigler, Dr. Paul B., 1991 - 1998 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Sikic, Manana, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Silva, Richard, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Silver, George (M.D.), 1973 - 1984 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Silverman, Richard, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Simmonds, Sofia, 1968, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Simon, John G., 1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Simon, Virginia, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Simonds-Bisbee, Pamela, 1982 - 1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Simpson, William K., 1963 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Sims, Christopher A., 1990 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Sinanoglu, Oktay, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Singer, Dr. Burton H., 1989 - 1991 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Singer, Dorothy (also see Jerome), 1985 - 1991 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Singer, Jerome (also see Dorothy), 1977 - 1991 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Siu, Helen, 1983 - 1986 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Skinner, Brian, 1982 - 2993 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Skinner, Catherine, 1977 - 1996 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Skowronek, Stephen, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Slayman, Caroline, 1984 - 1989 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Sledge, William (M.D.), 1995 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Sleeper, Herbert, Undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Slie, Rev. Samuel, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Smalley, Martha L., 1990 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Smith, Gaddis, 1981 - 1998 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Smith, John E., 1976 - 1992 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Smith, Laurence L., 1997 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Smith, Michael G., 1986 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Smith, Rogers M., 1984 - 2000 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Smith, Ronald B., 1986 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Smith, Steven B., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Smith, William H., 1977 - 1992 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Smooke, Mitchell D., 1994 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Soderstrom E. Jonathan, Undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Sofia, Sabatino, 1985 - 1992 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Soll, Dieta, 1982 - 1997 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Solnit, Albert, 1972 - 1993 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Sommerfield, Charles, 1964 - 1986 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Southwick, Wayne (M.D.), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Spangler, Stephanie (M.D.), 1990 - 1995 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Sparrow, Sara S., 1976 - 1988 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Spence, Jonathan, 1977 - 1990 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Speth, Gustav, 1997 - 1999 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Spinks, Bryan, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Spiro, Howard (M.D.), 1975 - 2000 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Spiegel, Herman D.J., 1972 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Spinelli, Catherine, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Sreenivasan, Prof. Katepalli, 1988 - 1999 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Srinivasan, T.N., Undated (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Stam, Allan, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Stankiewicz, Edward, 1975 - 1990 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Stanley, Valerie, 1983 - 1999 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Stansel, Horace Jr., 1977 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Starolis, Regina, Undated (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Starr, John B., 1978 - 1988 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Sterns, Janet E., 1984 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Steigman, Maury, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Steinberg, Mark D., 1990 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Steitz, Joan, 1982 - 1992 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Steitz, Thomas, 1987 - 1994 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Steitz, Thomas and Joan, 1997 - 1998 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Stempel, William D., 1987 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Stepto, Robert B., 1984 - 1993 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Stern, Howard, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Stern, Robert A.M., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Sternberg, Robert T., 1986 - 1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Stevens, Carroll D., 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Stevens, Donald, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Stevens, Joseph C., 1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Stewart, Barbara, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Stimson, Hugh M., 1985 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Stoertkuhl, Klemens, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Stoll, Steven B., 1996, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Stone, Douglas, Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Stone, Rose, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Stolwijk, Jan, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Storlazzi, Caesar T., 1985 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Stout, Harry, 1978 - 1987 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Stowe, Bruce B., Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Strauss, John (M.D.), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Strittmatter, Stephen, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Studdert-Kennedy, Michael, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Sturtevant, Julian M., Undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Suleri, Sara, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Sullivan, Danny, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Sullivan, Timothy, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Suttle, Lloyd, 1987 - 2001 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Swallow, John, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Swancutt, Diana, Undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Swartz, Stuart, Undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Swensen, David, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Swensen, David, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Symolon, Ethel, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Szary, Richard, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Szczarba, Robert H., 1996 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Szelenyi, Ivan, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Szwed, John, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Taffel, Max (M.D.), Undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Talner, Norman, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Tamagawa, Tsuneo, Undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Taub, Arthur (M.D.), Undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Taylor, Geneva B., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Taylor, "Tim", 1981 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Terry, Cynthia Rev., 1997 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Theodore, Eustace, 1988, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Thomas, Deborah G., 1999 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Thomas, Florence, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Thomas, Gerald E., 1991 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Thomas, James, 1982, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Thompson, Bradbury, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Thompson, Leonard M., 1986 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Thompson, Norma, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Thurston, Michael, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Tilson, John Q., Jr., Undated (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Tilton, Jim, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Tipton, Jennifer, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Tirro, Frank P., 1983 - 1997 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Tobin, James, 1981 - 2002 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Toelle, Hedwig, Undated (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Toffler, Robert (M.D.), Undated (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Touloukian, Robert (M.D.), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Trachtenberg, Alan, 1982 - 1992 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Trachtenberg, Betty, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Treat, Teresa Ann, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Treffers, Henry P., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Trinkaus, John P., 1987 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Trombetta, Jeffrey, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Tucker, Robert C., Undated (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Tufte, Edward R., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Tully, John C., 1997 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Tunney, Brian J., 1995 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Turekian, Karl, 1986 - 1994 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Turnbull, Gordon, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Turner, Diane, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Turner, Frank M., 1981 - 2000 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Turner, Henry A. Jr., 1989 - 1996 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Turner, Paul, Undated (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Turner, Rev. Philip III, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Udry, Chris, Undated (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Underdown, David, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Undegrove, Daniel, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Vaccaro, Patrick H., 1991 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Vaisnys, Elona M., 1999 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Vaisnys, Juozas R., Undated (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Valesio, Paolo, 1980 - 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Vallone, Peter D., 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Van Altena, William, 1980 - 1987 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Vandevelde, James, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Varmus, Harold, Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Vedrani, Ronald W., 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Vees, Jack, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Verdery, Benjamin, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Vermeule, Blakie, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Veronis, George, 1979 - 1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Vincent-Daviss, Diana, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Vignery, Agnes, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Vivian, James, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Vogel, David H., 1982 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Vogel, Susan, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Vogt, Daniel J., Undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Vogt, Daniel and Kristina, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Voight, Garth K., 1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Volf, Miroslav, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Volkmar, Fred R. (M.D.), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - VonStaden, Heinrich, 1985 - 1992 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Vose, Donna, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Vroom, Victor H., 1988 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Waage, Karl M., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - wagner, Allan R., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Wagner, Gunter, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Waid, Candace, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Waith, Eugene M., Undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Waksman, Byron H., Undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Waldfogel, Joel, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Walker, Brett, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Walker, Charles A., 1984 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Wallach, Glen, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Walsoe-Engel, Ingrid, 1989, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Wandel, Lee Palmer, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Wandycz, Piotr, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Wang, Shaoguang, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Ward, Richard, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Warfel, William B., 1993 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Wargo, John P., 1993 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Warren, Richard, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Wasserman, Harry, 1980 - 1998 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Waterman, Talbot, H, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Waters, Donald, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Waxman, Merle, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Weaver, Jace G. (Prof), 1999 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Webb, Jean, Undated (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Wedgewood, Ruth, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Wegener, Peter P., 1981 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Weimer, Jay, Undated (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Weinstein, Stanley, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Weiss, Harvey, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Weiss, Robert M. (M.D.), 2001 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Weissberg, Roger, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Welch, G. Harold, Jr., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Wellek, Rene, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Wellington, Sheila, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Welsh, Alexander, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Welsh, Alexander, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Wesselink, Adriaan J., Undated (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - West, Leslie, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Westerfield, H. Bradford, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Wheeler, Britt, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Wheeler, Stanton, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Whitker, Thomas R., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - White, Colin, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Whitehead, Maxine, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Whitney, Beverly, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Whobrey, William, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Wiberg, Kenneth B., 1989 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Wiesel, Elie, 1980 - 1987 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Wiedenbach, Ernestine, Undated (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Wilfley, Denise, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Williams, Gordon, Undated (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Williams, Linda, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Wilson, Keith L., Undated (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Wilson, Ransom, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Wilson, robert R., 1991 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Winchell, Horace, Undated (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Winer, Herbert, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Winks, Robin W., 1983 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Winnie, Prof. Laurence, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Wiseman, Carter, 1986 - 1991 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Wittink, Dick R., Undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Wizner, Rachel, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Wizner, Stephen, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Wojewodski, Stan, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Wolf, Bryan, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Wollaeger, Mark, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Wolterstorff, Nicholas, Undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Wood, Christopher S., Undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Wood, Richard J., 2000 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Woodall, Jerry, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Woodward, C. Vann, 1977 - 1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Woody, Sheila, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Worrell, Albert, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Wright, Craig, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Wu, King Lui, 1965 - 1988 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Wyckoff, Harold W., 1970 - 1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Wyman, Robert J., 1969 - 1990 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Wynn, Karen, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Wynne, Marjorie, 1983 - 1987 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Yandle, Stephen, 1986 - 1987 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Yarick-Cross, Doris, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Yeazell, Ruth B., 1995 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Yeigh, Bjong, Undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Yesner, Raymond (M.D.), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Yiengpruksawan, Mimi, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Yionoulis, Evan, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - York, Judy, Undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Young, Jamie, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Yu, Kyung Hak, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Zallinger, Rudolph, 1970 - 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Zaret, Barry, 1983 - 1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Zdanys, Jonas, 1984 - 1993 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Zeller, Michael E., 1986 - 1996 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Zettergren, Jane M., 1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Zigler, Edward F., 1985 - 1995 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Zilm, Kurt W., 1987 - 1991 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Zuckerman, Bernard, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Zweig, Felix, 1978 - 1987 (Box 20, Folder 9)